I want everyone to go on their knees for their country, continent and nation
and cry to God for redemption.
Now, it's everywhere.
Everywhere.
Dry bones shall rise again!
Whatever spots, whatever challenges - there is no single nation without challenges.
And the challenges are causing uproar.
Right now, open your lips and say to the Lord:
"Here we are on our knees with humility, with all our heart,
I pray for my nation. I pray for countries. I pray for continents - troubled ones.
Father, come at this time and intervene."
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
God's intervention in the whole world, God's intervention, we need God's intervention in the whole world.
We're praying against war in the whole world, We're praying against war in Africa,
We're praying against the wrath of God on all the land, We need God's intervention in the whole world.
God's intervention in the whole world, God's intervention, we need God's intervention in the whole world.
You've got the whole world in Your hands!
Don't forget the nations that rescue nationes - they're too facing their own challenges.
Open your lips for prayer.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Don't forget the nation, Nigeria. There's peace - that is why we're here today.
Pray for the leaders and the nation. Thank you. Hallelujah!
In Jesus' Christ name we pray.
Thank you very much. Raise up!